fallenlondon.com 2014-03-26

# 

**FAILBETTER GAMES**

 **StoryNexus Privacy Policy  
** Last updated on 21st August 2012

These Privacy Policy forms part of an agreement between you and Failbetter Games Ltd (referred to in these Terms as "FBG", "we", "our" and "us") and applies to your use of FBG's storygame creation platform StoryNexus, its database, website and other channels and technologies through which StoryNexus content may be created or played, and when this Privacy Policy mentions "StoryNexus" or "the Service", this includes all of these things.

If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use StoryNexus.  If you have any queries, please email us at enquiries@storynexus.com

 **Introduction**

1\.     FBG is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

2\.     This privacy policy sets out the basis on which we will process any personal information as well certain other information we collect from you, or that you provide to us.  Please read this privacy policy carefully so that you understand how we will treat your information.

 **A quick word about children**

3\.     We recognise we have a special obligation to protect personal information we obtain from children.  We do not and will not knowingly collect information from any unsupervised child under the age of 13.  In certain countries, prior written permission or other verifiable consent may also be required from a parent or guardian for children under the age of 18.

 **The Data Controller**

4\.     For data collection purposes, the data controller is Failbetter Games Limited, a company registered in England and Wales with number 07121579.

 **Information we may collect from you**

5\.     We respect your right to privacy and will only process personal information you provide to us in accordance with applicable privacy laws, such as the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 within the EU.

6\.     The kinds of data which we may process in order to monitor our Service and improve your user experience include:

  * Your email address.
  * Your screen name and profile picture.

Technical or other details about any device which you use to access the Services: Internet and/or network connection (including your IP address, Media Access Control (MAC); operating system, browser type or other software; hardware (including computer hardware) or other technical details.

Details of your use of StoryNexus including, but not limited to: traffic data, location/geographical data, the Service resources that you access, the time you spend on the Service, crash reports and reasons for connection drops.

7\.     We may collect and process data about you through the following means:

  * Data that you provide to us as part of obtaining access to our Services (for example, signing up for a StoryNexus account, providing a support email address for a World which you have created).
  * Information provided when you report a problem with any of the Services.

We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.

8\.     We may collect this data through our Services or third party services connected with them.

9\.     We store the data that we collect from you in our servers in the EU.  However, this data may be transferred to, and stored at, a location outside of the European Economic Area ("EEA").  It may also be processed by staff operating outside of the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers.  Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the performance of our obligations from any contracts entered into with you and the provision of support services.  By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.  We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

10\.     We use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting on this site, in order to learn about the kind of users that visit our site, and possibly target future advertising or tune our content based on that. All data is anonymised and we don't match it to usernames, email addresses or any other personally identifying information.

Do note this browser add-on:

 **https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/**

which will allow you to opt out of Google Analytics entirely, meaning that none of the previous paragraph applies to you.

 **Cookies**

10\.   Our website uses cookies to collect information about you.  We use cookies to identify you over the course of a single session, and to store transient data about your recent use of the Service in order to improve your user experience. We do not use shared or advertising cookies.

You will already have confirmed that you accept the placement of cookies on your machine when first entering our website.  However should you now wish to choose to refuse cookies, please click here. You may also change your website browser settings to reject cookies.  For further information about cookies, including how to refuse cookies, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org. Please note that disabling cookies may affect the functionality of the Service.

 **Uses made of your information**

11\.   We use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To authenticate with the Service: this may include email address, password, Twitter authentication name and tokens, Facebook authentication name and tokens. We do not share this information with third parties.
  * To ensure that content from the Service is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer or other device from which you access the Service.
  * To provide you with information or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, if you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * To perform our obligations from any contracts entered into with you.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service, if you choose.
  * To notify you about changes to our Service.
  * We may use your authentication information to find your contacts on social networks, and allow you to invite them to join you in the Service. We will not do this without your active consent.
  * We may use your authentication information to allow you to message other users. We will not do this without your active consent.

12\.   Please remember that any communications you have via our Service may reveal details about you, including for example your account name and/or the content of your communications to other users.  World creators will be aware of the quantity and purpose of any virtual currency purchases you have made in their worlds.

13\.   We are not responsible for the activities of other users or other third parties to whom you choose to provide your personal information (whether via our Service or otherwise).

 **Disclosure of your information**

14\.   We may disclose your personal information to any member of our existing or future group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries.

15\.   We may disclose your personal information to third parties in the following circumstances:

  * If you have created a world, your username may be displayed in connection with that world.    
  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal information to the seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If we or substantially all of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal information held by us about our customers will be a transferred asset.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal information in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms; or to protect our rights, property, or safety of our customers, or others.
  * We may share aggregated information that does not include personal information for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. Any information shared in these contexts will be anonymised.

16\.  We will not use your information for third party marketing purposes.

 **Third party sites**

17\.   Our Services may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates.  These websites have their own privacy policies.  Please note that if you follow a link to any of these websites, we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies, nor do we endorse such websites.

 **Your rights**

18\.   You can also email us at support@storynexus.com to request that we delete your personal information from our database. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honour your request.  We may retain an archived copy of your records if required to do so by law or for legitimate business purposes.

 **Data security**

19\.   Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. We will do our best to protect your personal information but we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Services - any transmission is at your own risk. We will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access to your information.

 **Changes to our privacy policy**

20\.   Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by email.  We will indicate the changes clearly.

 **Contact**

21\.   Please address any questions or comments regarding this privacy policy to enquiries@storynexus.com
